Claudia Forero

C: 786-4591608 petenaguela@hotmail.com

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Jan 2001 - Dec 2003 Universidad de la Sabana (Bogotá Colombia) Bachelor of Social Comunication.

July 2003 – Mar 2007 Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano (Bogota Colombia) Bachelor of Advertisiong and Marketing.

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

Highly creative Specialist with excellent skills in Production, Radio and Television. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; passionate and inventive creator of innovative marketing strategies and campaigns for media industry; accustomed to performing in deadline-driven environments with an emphasis on working within budget requirements.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WORK

*Feb 2013 KSC Kreate, Hollywood Producer for Wallmart commertial.

*Sept 2012, EF Scenes Miami, Fl Creative direction, Avianca presentation.

*Agst 2012 The Brand Shop, Miami, Fl Executive Producer, Mega TV.

*Jun 2012 Aqui En Deportes, Miami, Fl Sport Reporter for TV Show.

*Sep-Oct 2010 FML studio, Bogota, COL Host for TV show.

*Mar-Apr 2010 Loop, Bogota, COL Producer for TV Commertial. *September, 2007-April 2009 Comobar 2000, Miami, Fl Commertial Producer and Direction, Entertainment TV Show.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Oct 2008 - Sept 2010 The Brand Shop

Advertasing and Marketing (Miami FL)

* Advertisiong, Marketing and social media For production Companies.

Oct 2011 - Oct 2012 Miami Herald

Advertasing and Marketing (Miami FL)

* Event coordination and social media.

Oct 2012 - Oct 2013 Canal UNO (Bogota Colombia)

Host, Producer for Electronic Musik TV

- * Host of entertainment Tv show
- * Producer of different episodes of the Electronic Musik TV.

Oct 2013 - Present, Los Dueños del Balon Radio Sportscaster.

*writter, reporter of the different daily episodes.

*Prepare, and develope concepts for the season.

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCY

Mac And Windows Software

- Microsoft Office
- o Power Point